想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
-你好
-Hello
请出示证件
Documents Please
好的
Yes
能问个问题吗？
机票是公司出钱的
Can I ask you a question?
This ticket was actually paid by a company
我能把积累里程放在我个人的名下吗？
Do you know if you can place the miles
Under my name?
不能，这张票不在积累里程范围之内。
No. This ticket doesn't include miles
好吧，我没有要问的了
Oh, well. In that case I won't ask anything
3号登机口已经可以登机了
They are already boarding through gate 3
谢谢
Thanks
我来帮你
I'll help you
好的
All right
工作还是旅行？
Work or pleasure?
我希望都有
Both things, I hope
你是做什么的
What do you do?
我是个模特
I'm a model
对不起，我应该能想到的
Excuse me, I should've imagined
谢谢
Thanks
你做时装秀还是广告？
Fashion show or advertisement
时装秀
Fashion Show
你呢？
You?
-你是做什么的？
-What do you do?
-我被你打败了
-You killed me there
为什么？
Why?
那个“你”已经让我深陷第五层地狱了
That "you" dropped me to the 5th level of hell
我得把我自己拯救出来
I will need to fix myself right up from this
我是个音乐评论人
I'm a music critic
我知道这个听起来很糟
It sounds horrible, I know
不啊，评论摇滚吗？
No. Rock?
现在你想拯救我了？
Now you want to fix it?
古典音乐
Classical music
我第一个男朋友是个古典音乐人
My first boyfriend was a classical musician
其实他是学古典音乐的
In fact he studied classical music
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
没什么，他不出名
No, he is not known
我们在一起的时候他还试着搞点什么作品出来
He tried to present some works when we
were together
但是据我所知他从没发表过
But as far as I know he never published
或者编篡过...不对...那词儿怎么说？
Or edited...No... How do you say it?
随便怎么说，我会自动转换成专业术语
You choose the term you want and I'll install it
in the artistic community
他叫Pasternak.Gabriel Pasternak
Pasternak. Gabriel Pasternak
Pasternak
先声明我是个掘坟人不是评论人
Knowing this I would've told you I'm grave digger and not a critic
他在音乐学院参加比赛的时候我是评审团的主席之一
He presented his thesis in the contest of the conservatory
when I was a the president of the jury
我把他淘汰了
I kicked him out of it
是的，我当时和他在一起
Yes, I was with him at the time
这对他伤害太大了
It was tremendous what they did to him
他看了评论以后一周都没下床
He passed a week in bed after reading the critic
有时候事情就是这样。我必须伤害一些可怜人儿的自尊
Sometimes it's like that. I have to hurt a poor devil's self esteem
来保护大家的耳朵不受污染
In order to protect the ears of a whole population
我可能会犯错误，不过这件事情...
Eventually I can make mistakes, but in this case this was a...
太让人厌恶了
An unpresentable abomination
你还和他在一起吗？
Do you still see him?
不，我们最后没在一起
No, we didn't end up very well
不过我还在意他
I still care for him, though
他不是个坏人
He wasn't a bad person
我不知道，但是在比赛的时候表演出那样的东西
I don't know that, but to present something like that in a contest
他肯定有什么问题
Some problem he has to have
Gabriel Pasternak，我怎么能忘了他Gabriel Pasternak, how can I forget him
我们为这事儿笑了好几个月
We all laughed at it for months
抱歉打扰您了
Sorry I interrupt you but
我无意中听到了你们的谈话
I was eavsdropping the conversation
我不敢相信这么巧
I can't believe so much coincidence
我是Gabriel Pasternak在Palomer第七中学的老师
I was the teacher of Gabriel Pasternak in the school #7 of Palomar
我以前通知过他要复读一年，这太难了
I had the difficult task of informing him that he was repeating the year
我能证明那孩子有问题
I can testify that the kid had problems
我教了十三年书从来没见过那样的事
In thirty years of teaching I've never saw something like it
他像刚出生的婴儿又哭又叫
He screamed and cried like a newborn baby
-Leguizamón老师？
-Mrs. Leguizamón?
-是的
-Yes
我是Ignacio Fontana。还记得我吗？
I'm Ignacio Fontana. Do you remember me?
Ignacio Fontana，这太不可思议了
Ignacio Fontana. This is incredible
这是冥冥之中的巧合啊
There's a cosmic connection here
-pasternak和你是同班吗？
-Wasn't pasternak your classmate?
-是的
-Yes
-你们是朋友吗？
-Are you friends？
-是的，最好的朋友
-Oh yes, best friends
可怜的家伙，我们老欺负他
Poor dude. We used to bully him a lot
这更不可思议了
This is more than incredible
我是家得宝家具店的经理，你们说的这伙计在我这儿工作过一阵儿
I was a Home Depot manager, where this fellow that you speak of
worked for a while
他总和顾客发生矛盾，我不得不炒了他Since he always had a problem with his clients I had to fire him
-我当时...
-When I...
-不好意思，这儿还有人认识Gabriel Pasternak吗？
-Sorry, someone else knows Gabriel Pasternak?
-我
-Yes
-我认识他
-I know him
-我认识
-I do
为什么你们都在这个飞机上？你们自费买的票吗？
Why are you in this flight? Did you buy the tickets?
不是
No
我在房地产工作，雇主让我去看看待售的农场
I worked for real estate and they sent me to see some farms for sale
我是出差去见预约的旅游秘书
In my job they made an appointment for me to go see the
secretary of tourism
我是抽奖赢的机票，他们说我不能改签
I won it at a raffle, they said I couldn't change the date
我必须得坐今天的飞机
I either flew today or nothing
Gabriel Pasternak是这飞机的机长
Gabriel Pasternak is the captain of this flight
我们在一起训练，我们曾经是朋友，但是有一回他请我约会被我拒绝了，他就开始...
We trained together. We were friends, but when he invited me out
and I said no and he started to...
不过现在没关系了，起飞以后我给他送咖啡...
It doesn't matter now. After we took off I gave him coffee...
门锁了，飞行员也不回答，天啊我该怎么办
The door is locked. The pilots are not answering.
I'm desperate, I don't know what to do
我和他唯一的朋友背着他偷情
I cheated on him with his only friend
和他
With him
Gabriel！你在这儿吗？
Gabriel! Are you there?
我是Victor Llensen，请和我说句话
I'm Victor Llensen, speak to me please!
-你是谁
-Who are you
-我是他多年的心理医生
-I was his psychiatrist for years
有一回我延长了治疗时间，他就生了气再也没回来过了
At some point I augmented his session time.
He got angry and he never came back
Gabriel，听我说
Gabriel, listen to me
你不必为任何事责怪自己
You don't have to blame yourself for anything
你是受害者
You are the victim of this situation
说白了是你的父母毁了你的生活
I'm saying it plain and simple. The ones who ruined your life
were your parents
从你出生开始他们就对你要求太多了
Since you were born they've been asking you for too much
他们让你饱受挫折，他们要为你的痛苦负责
They placed on you all their frustration.
They are the responsibles of your suffering
Gabriel，我们都和这些没关系
All of us here, Gabriel, don't have anything to do with this
晚上好，您一位吗？
Good evening, a table for one?
你数学真好
I see you're good at math
一位，好的
One, yes
请随便坐
Sit wherever you want
今天的特色菜是小扁豆和米饭
The special for today is lentils with rice
听着不错
Sounds delicious
那么
So?
唉
Hey
那个人是我同乡
That guy is from my town
他是个篡夺者
An usurper
腐败的政客
A corrupt politician
他拍卖了我们的房子
He auctioned our house
因为他我爸爸自杀了
And because of him my dad committed suicide
葬礼后两周
Two weeks after the burial
他想勾引我妈妈
He tried to hit on my mom
他经常跟踪她
He stalked her so much
所以我们搬到这儿了
That we had to move here
你知道多少次我梦见这样和他相遇？
Do you know for how long I've dreamed to have him like this?
就这样站在我面前
In front of me
我必须得和他说些什么
I will have to and say something to him
对他说些什么？
Say something to him?
你爸爸因为他自杀了
Thanks to that guy your father committed suicide
你唯一要做的事就是侮辱他？
And the only thing you plan to do is to insult him?
为什么我们不把老鼠药放在饭里毒死他
Why don't we put rat poison in his food?
就在后厨这儿
There's in the back
剂量正好的话，五分钟他的心脏就会炸了
A good dosis and in five minutes his heart will explode
今天生意很忙?
A lot of work today?
这么大雨不会的
Not with this rain
那我叫你这么多次你怎么不来
I'm asking because I've been calling you for a while
你得负责招待客人，亲爱的
You have to look over here, darling
对不起
My apologies
想好要点什么了吗
Do you know what are you going to order?
我要薯条煎蛋(译：不知道是什么菜)
Bring my fries with eggs
我要是还饿的话会要别的
If I'm still hungry I will ask for something else
饮料呢？
Any beverages?
健怡可乐
Diet Coke
健怡可乐？
Diet Coke?
健怡
Diet
可乐
Coke
薯条.煎蛋
Fries. With eggs
你想让我给你写下来？
Do you want me to write it for you?
我恨他，我恨他
I hate him. I hate him
给他做薯条煎蛋
Make him some fries with eggs
老鼠药
[RAT POISON]
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
你想让我进监狱？
Do you want me to go to jail?
监狱？
Jail?
你相信FBI会给那个混蛋尸检吗
Do you believe the FBI is going to make an autopsy
on that prick?
薯条煎蛋
Fires with eggs
他们会认为是他是胆固醇太高才死的
They are going to think that it was the cholesterol
你给他做薯条煎蛋吧
Can you make him the fries with eggs?
我能问问你在某些事情上的意见吗？
Can I ask for your opinion on something?
你看着像个细心的女孩，来这儿
Since you seem to be an atentive girl. Come here
你喜欢哪个？这个？
Which one do you like. This one?
或者这个？
Or this one?
我喜欢红的
I'll choose the red one
红的，等等
The red one. Wait. Wait.
你觉得我在这张照片上看着太严肃了吗
Do you think I look too serious in this picture?
不，我觉得挺好的
No, I think it looks fine
谢谢
Thank you
并且监狱也不是太差
Besides jail is not that bad
它只是公众影响不好
It just has bad publicity
他们给你吃的
They give you food
你不用付房租
You don't pay rent
你无忧无虑地生活
You live with no worries
如果找对了狱友圈子，你会玩儿得很开心的
And if you have good group
you'll have a lot of fun
一起打桥牌
You play bridge
你在监狱里待过？
You were in jail?
待过一段时间
For some time
我保证在里面我更自由
And I can assure I felt more free there
这个餐厅真是个破地方
This is a shithole
你做了什么进了监狱
And wht did you do?
我不会后悔的事
Nothing that I regret
并且他还要竞选市长
Besides he is going to run for mayor
那个混蛋，你能相信吗
That son of a bitch. Can you believe it?
怎么不相信，那些混蛋现在都统治世界了
How am I not going to believe it when those bastards
rule the world
清醒点，姑娘
Wake up, girl!
你觉得怎么样
What do you say
我们要为这个社会做点好事吗
Do we make a favor for the community?
太好了
Perfect
你放了老鼠药
You put the rat posion!
别装无辜，你早看见了
Don't play like a naive girl. Tell me you
didn't noticed it
这个国家就是这么做事的
That's how this country runs
每个人都想报复这种混蛋，但是从没人敢动一根指头
Everybody wants give this characters what they deserve
but nobody wants to move a finger
自豪吧，姑娘
Feel proud about it, girl
你终于在你悲惨的生活中做了点有意义的事了
For once in your miserable life you are
doing something worthy
嘿！我什么也没做
Hey! I'm not doing anything here
没做？跟我商量毒死他而不是撤掉他盘子的可是你
No? You keep discussing with me instead of taking away his plate?
放松，你什么事也不用担心
Calm down. You don't have to worry about anything
审问的时候我会说是我今天早上在厨房放了老鼠药
In the investigation I'm going to say that this morning
I was placing poison in the kitchen
因为这儿到处长虫子，这也确实是真的
Because everything was full of bugs, which on the other hand
it is completely true
有一小块药恰好掉到盘子里了，警方又能说什么
And that coincidentally a little rock got inside a pan.
What are they going to tell me
这真是疯了
This is madness
嘿，这破药没过期，对吧？
Hey, this shit wasn't expired, right?
上面没写保质期
It doesn't say the expiring date
老鼠药要是过期了
How was it?
会怎么样
When a poison is expired
毒性更强还是更弱？
Is it more or less deadly
-你好吗
-Everything fine?
-当然
-Yes
坐这儿
Sit right there
喝点什么，Alexis？
What will you drink, Alexis
不知道，芬达？
I don't know. A Fanta?
-我把这个热一下怎么样？
-What if I got heat these up a little?
-不用了，不用了，放这儿就行
-No, no, leave it there
需要热的话我会叫你
If i need you to heat them up I'll ask you
能给他来瓶芬达吗
Could you bring him a Fanta, please?
我受够这姑娘了
I'm fed up with this girl
我们得做点儿什么，他俩现在都在吃
We have to do something, both are eating now
到底放了毒药吗
Do we put more posion?
他是个孩子！
He's a kid!
不过他会长大的，变得跟他爹一个德行
But he is going to grow. Like father like son
斩草要除根
It's better if we finish with all the weed right now
嘿，我感觉不太舒服
Hey, I don't think I'm feeling right
你怎么了
What is happening to you?
你还好吗
Are you ok?
-不好意思，这菜肯定都冷了
-Excuse me, this has to be freezing by now
-别动，放在这儿
-No, leave it there!
谁他妈的教你这么工作的，能让人好好吃饭吗
Who the fuck taught you to work like these
Could you let people eat in peace?
看看这疯婆子
Will you look at these fucking bitch
等等，爸爸
Wait, dad
你现在要把这些都捡起来
Now you are going to pick them all up
你要把这些捡起来
You are going to pick them up
-Isabel，叫救护车
-Isabel, call the ambulance!
-一个一个来
-One by one!
吃我一刀
Take this!
再来一刀
Here you go!
我要像弄小鸡一样弄死你
I'm going to butcher your liver like a chicken
傻瓜，赶快让开
Come on. Move, moron
你这家伙出了什么毛病
What's up with you, dude?
真是个无耻的废物
What a shameless douchbag
你他妈的是个蠢蛋
You're a motherfucking wetbag
混账
Jerk!
主啊，让我耐心点
Mother, give me patience
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
你好，我在Salta和Buenos Aires的交界处
Hello, I'm here around the 60th km
大约60公里处
Of the route the connects Salta with Buenos Aires
是的，车牌号是U-I-A 7-1-9
Yes, U-I-A 7-1-9
Diego Iturralde
很好
Very good.
我说我在在Salta到Buenos Aires和Cafayate的交界60公里的地方
I was telling you that I got a flat tire around
the 60th km
车胎漏气了
Of the route that connects Salta to Buenos Aires,
with Cafayate
我想知道你们什么时候才能来
And I wanted to know how long will you guys take
to come here because
车是新的，而且我换胎技术不好
The car is new and I'm not that good with the jack
发生了什么？你被吓着了吗？
What happened?
Did you get scared?
快点，哥们儿，快走
Come on, man, keep going
快点，快走
Come on. Go on
行行好，我可不想打架
Please, I don't want to fight
如果我冒犯了，还请你原谅
If I offended you, forgive me
如果冒犯了真是对不起
I'm sorry if I offended you
行了
Well
满意了吗
Happy?
完事儿了吗
Are you done?
小心...
Wacth out with the...
你干什么呢，快停下来
What are you doing? Stop!
得了吧，我可什么都没对你做
Come on, man, I didn't do anything to you
你怎么不把之前骂我的话再说一遍，怎么样
Why don't you shout me again what you said before.
How did it go?
哦天啊
Oh God
我的天啊
My god
我已经说了对不起了，你还想让我做什么
I already told you I'm sorry, I don't know what else
do you want me todo
如果需要的话我会下车，可我觉得这没必要
If I get to get off the car I will, but I think
it's unnecesary
操你..停下！
Motherfu... Stop!
操你妈的
Motherfucker
下午好，警官
Good afternoon, officer.
我在大概在Salta到Buenos Aires和Cafayate的交界处的60公里处
I'm around the 60th km of the route that connects Salta
to Buenos Aires with Cafayate
有个人袭击我
There is an individual who is attacking me
他有武器，你们打不过他的
It is armored, you'll not be able to break it!
混蛋
Fag!
这男的车牌号是...
The license plate of the man is.
我看不见，你们现在能把警车开过来吗
I cannot see it, but could you bring a police car right now?
太好了
Perfect
快点，这人疯了
Hurry up. This man is out of control
我确定他们在来的路上
I'm sure they'll be coming now
好了，快停下，求你了
Well, stop now, man. Please!
你毁了我的车，走开
You destroyed my car! Go away!
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
我操，操你妈的
Fucking shit. This motherfucker
不，操你妈的，王八蛋
No, motherfucker. Fuck your mother, asshole!
No! Motherfucker! Asshole!
求你了，求你了
Please. Please!
妈的
Fuck
混蛋
Faggot!
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
王八蛋
Asshole!
你死定了
You're dead!
我知道你车牌号了，王八蛋
I know your license plate, asshole!
你听见了吗
Did you hear me?
我知道你车牌号了，是U-I-A!
I know your license plate, U-I-A!
我会找到你我要杀了你
I'm going to search you and I'm going to kill you!
重新计算路线
Recalculating
指挥中心，这是29号车，请确认事发地点
Base. This is unit 29. Can you confirm the km, please?
等等，指挥中心，等等
Attention, base. Attention
你推断发生了什么，探长
What hypothesis do you have, detective
冲动发生的犯罪？
Crime of passion?
外面怎么样了
How is everything outside?
都准备好了，Simon
Everything is ready, Simón
谢谢
Thanks
咱们开始吧
Let's go
注意，我们要引爆了
Attention, we are going to detonate
5,4,3
Five, Four, Three
Two
限制区域
[RESTRICTED AREA]
放这儿，谢谢
There, thank you
在这儿签名
Sign here
好的，亲爱的
Yes, honey.
不，我要去我办公室看有没有语音信息，然后就走
No, I'm going to go to my office to check the voicemail
and then I'll leave
我会带着蛋糕5点去的，别担心
I'm going to be there at 5 with the cake.
Don't worry
5点，带着蛋糕，别担心，我不会忘了
At 5 I'm there with the cake. Don't worry,
I'll not forget it
我希望你喜欢蛋糕的样子
I hope you like how it looks
当然，她会非常喜欢的，谢谢
Yes, she's going to love it. Thank you
一共360块
It will be 360
它是进口的吗
Was it imported?
一，二，能给我张账单吗
One, two... Can you give me a bill?
我们有羊角面包，"治安委员"
Yes, we have croissants, "vigilantes"
票，账单
The ticket. Bill
哦，是的，当然，我会带来的
Oh! yes, of course. I'll bring it
他们一定是一群蠢蛋
They had to be a bunch of douchebags
请微笑，我们在拍你
[SMILE, WE ARE FILMING YOU]
下一个
Next!
你好
Hello
是这样的，我把车停在...
Look, I parked my car...
请出示驾驶证
Your license, please
好的
Yes
请好好跟我说话
Talk to me nicely, please
我在好好跟你说话啊，先生
I'm talking to you nicely, sir
可能吧
More or less
拖车费用是430比索，我们会把发单寄到你的地址
The towing service will be 430 pesos and you we will
send the fine to your address
好的，但是你没听我的解释
Yes, but you're not listening to what I want to explain
人行道根本就没划线
The sidewalk was completely unpainted
我不可能知道这里是禁止停车的
There was no possible way that I could know that the place
was a no-parking area
我明白
I understand
我懂了，如果你想从这儿把车开走，你必须付拖车费用，好吗
I see. Now, if you want to retreive the vehicle from here
You will have to pay the towing service. Ok?
然后，你可以在工作日申请退款
Later, if you want you can make a withdrawal from monday to friday,
from eight to fourteen hours
请找一楼211房间的Carlos Pellegrini.
In the address Carlos Pellegrini 211, first floor
嗯..不，你知道我们会做什么吗
Hmm. No. Do you know what we are going to do?
我会让你找遍你能找的人
I'm going to ask you to go and talk to whoever you have to
我想不花一分钱就取走我的车
I want to take my car without paying a penny
我想让你赔我到这儿的打车钱
I want you to give me what I paid
for the taxi to get here and
并且给我一个真诚的道歉
And that you give my respective apologies
你笑什么，我是认真的
What are you laughing about, I'm being serious
那种当他们错了会给你道歉的办公室在哪儿
Where is the office where they give you your apologies
when they make a mistake?
我们是一条船上的，先生，请快点
We are all in the same boat, sir. Hurry up, please
你看，罚单上说你的车停在了禁停区
Look. The ticket said your car
was in a no-parking zone
我会再重复一遍，我们不需要更多的证据
We don't need more proof than that.
I'll repeat again
你想取车就得付钱
If you want to take your car you have to pay
如果不行请你离开，我们还要继续工作
If that's not the case I'll ask you to leave
and let me continue working
我要是没有现金呢
And if I don't have cash?
可以用信用卡，借钱，或者改天再来
You can pay it with credit, debit,
or you can come another day.
不管怎样，我们都要收到罚款
However, we will charge you for the car
parked here
你知道你是个罪犯吗
Did you know that you're a criminal?
-我只是在做我的工作
-I'm doing my jobe here
-不是
-No
协助犯罪的人也是罪犯
The ones who work for criminals are
other criminals
当然，这也是一种看待问题的方法
Well, it's a way of looking at it
悲惨的公务员
Miserable public worker
腐败的公共服务系统
Of this corrupt system
谢谢，日安
Thank you, have a nice day
你出生的时候我们和你在一起
We were with you when you were born
当你收到第一个玩具
When you received your first toys
我快到了
[I'M ARRIVING]
别来了，人都快走完了
[DON'T COME, ALMOST EVERYBODY LEFT]
祝你生日快乐，祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday to you. Happy Birthday to you
祝亲爱的Camila生日快乐
Happy Birthday dear Camila.
Happy Birthday to you
生日快乐，亲爱的
Happy Birthday, honey
让他们再唱一遍
Tell them to sing again
别跟我说话，Simon
Don't even talk to me, Simón
你好，亲爱的，生日快乐
Hello, darling. Happy Birthday
你好孩子们
Hello kids
你好吗，Antonio
How are you, Antonio
你好，亲爱的，一切都很好
Hello, dear! Everything's good
-嗨，你好吗
-Hello. How are you
-我们要走了
-We were leaving
等等，我和你一块儿走
Wait, I'll come with you
你就不能先打车过来，完事之后再去取车
Couldn't you take a taxi and take the car later?
-不能！
-No! No!
-你错过了你女儿的生日聚会
-You missed your daughter's brithday, Simón
你觉得什么事都简单，我已经厌倦了人们从我身上拿钱
Everything is so easy for you.
I'm just tired of people taking my money
人行道绝对没划线！
The sidewalk was absolutely unpainted!
你知道这让我多生气吗
Do you have any idea of the anger this produces on me?
你事事责怪别人让我很生气你知道吗
Do you have any idea of the anger this produces on me
that you always blame everything?
你事事都抱怨社会
That you have to blame society for everything
今天是车，昨天是交通，明天没准是抗议集会
Today it was the car. Yesterday it was the traffic.
Tomorrow will be the protest
事实是你本来可以早点到这儿
The truth is that you were perfectly capable
of leaving earlier
你还能帮我组织聚会
You could've helped me organize the party
你也能来迎接你女儿的客人
And you would be ready to receive your daughter's guests
但是事情不是这样的，你觉得什么事都比家庭优先
But no. Everything is a priority except
your family
-不
-No
-而我像个傻子似的站在这儿，想着你能改变
-And I am standing here like an idiot
Thinking that you'll change
你知道吗？
And you know what?
社会是不会变的
Society will not change
你也不会变
You will not change
我已经受够了
And I am tired of it
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
你是工程师，你来算算
The engineer here is you.
Make the math
政府让私企白赚钱
The goverment lets a private company
make money for nothing
很明显是为了让我们去花政府让我们花的钱
Obviously in exchange for a payment that
we all have to choose
真不公平，不过事实就是这样的
It's indignant, but it'ss like that
你有两种选择
And you have two choices
要不然交了钱再工作赚回来
You either pay and work a little
要不然当街暴毙而亡
Or your heart explodes due to stress
你明白的
And you know what, man
我活着有很多原因
I have a lot of reasons to live
我想航海，和我的孙辈旅行
I want to sail.
Travel the world with my grandchildren
别生气
Don't get angry
-你好，早上好
-Hello. Good morning
-早上好
-Good morning
他们归档没问题，我也已经付了拖车费，不过这儿有误会
They filed this fine, and I already payed
the towing service. But there's an error
-因为人行道没划线
-Because the sidewalk was unpainted...
-能让我看看吗
-Would you let me see?
当然
Yes
一共560比索
It is 560 pesos
听着，我有点紧张，所以请听我说
Look. I'm a little nervous here
So I'll ask you to listen to me
人行道没划线，我认为你应该让人标明他们在哪儿拖走了我的车
The sidewalk was unpainted. I think you should
send someone to the address where they took my car
来证明我是对的
In order to verify that I'm right
然后，让市政府向我道歉，因为我是对的
Then, ask the city's government to
forgive me, because I'm right
还了我的钱，并且为我损失的时间赔偿
Give me back the money I paid.
AND pay me for all the time I've been wasting
罚单上写了车停在了禁停区
The ticket says that the car was
in a no-parking zone
这就是足够的证据
And that is considered enough proof
你必须付罚款560比索
The fine is 560 pesos that you HAVE to pay
如果不付我们会开始收利息
If you don't pay we will start charging interests
你在听吗
Are you listening to me?
足够的证据？去你妈的
Enough proof? Fuck off.
我是说路边没有画黄线
I'm telling you
the curb was not painted yellow
首先，请你不要侮辱我
First, I'm going to ask you
to stop insulting me
因为我在工作
Because I'm working here
其次，你需要好好了解法律的作用
Second, you should inform yourself
of how the law works
法律上没有不知者无罪这一说
The fact that you don't know the laws
does not excempt you from braking them
有天你杀了人还说：“我不知道不可以那么做。”你早进监狱了
Tomorrow you kill somebody and say
"I didn't know you couldn't do that"
You'll go to jail
没关系，没人告诉过你
That's fine, maybe nobody explained it to you
但是你还说会进监狱，你懂吗？
But you still go to jail.
Is it understandable?
你的例子不够贴切
This example that you just gave wasn't
very accurate
照这么说我得记住哪些街道能停车哪些不能
With that criteria I should know by heart
the streets where I can park and the ones where I can't
根本不用考虑划没划线
Without taking in account whether they are painted or not
对，这些信息在车管所的网站上都有
Exactly. The information is available in the website
of the Department of Mobile Vehicles
好吧，我想和你们经理谈谈
Ok. I need to talk with your manager, please
不能，这儿没有你可以谈的经理
No, there's no manager to call
没有？
No?
你以为你是谁？国家总统吗？
Who do you think you are?
The president of the country, moron?
先生，还有好多人等着呢
Sir, there's a lot of people
你要是不交罚款请让我继续工作
If you don't want to pay I'll ask you to let me work
当一个罪犯是什么感觉？来，告诉我
What does it feel like to be a criminal?
Come on, tell me
保安
Security in station seven
你要叫保安？太好了
Are you calling for security? Great!
我要声明，我维护我作为公民的权利，所以我是个罪犯
I am making a claim. I am defending as a citizen
and I'm a criminal
你要躲在后面叫保安
You have to be behind there
and call for security
你想叫保安吗
Do you want to call security?
叫保安啊，叫啊
Call security! Call it!
快叫保安
Now call for security!
放开我
Leave me!
请在这儿签名
Sign here, please
-我的天啊
-My god
-你怎么样了
-How are you doing
他们没强奸你吧？
They didn't rape you, right?
真是不敢相信，太不敢相信了
It's unbelievable.
Really unbelievable
真是疯了
What a madness
Seijas已经叫了公司的律师并且让他全权负责
Seijas sent a lawyer from the company
and told him to be in charge of everything
希望他好好干，因为最近...
I hope he plays it good because lately...
是，多多少少
Yeah, more or less.
你的名字就印在上面
Your name and last name appear there
车管所暴力事件
[VIOLENT REACTION IN THE DMV]
他们说你在公司工作
They mention that you work for the firm
（我大工行？）
Seijas的父母可不喜欢你闯的祸
Seija's partners didn't like the shit you pulled
市政府是我们的主顾之一
The city's government is one of our main clients!
他们要把你裁掉，Simon
They are going to cut you off, Simón
已经决定了
It has been decided
我明白你现在没有工作，Fischer先生
I understand that at this moment you don't have a job, Mr. Fischer
是的，问这个干吗
Yes. Why you ask?
这是一种犯罪吗
Is it a crime?
我没说这是犯罪，对吧？
I didn't say it was a crime, right?
对，但是我觉得我听出了谴责的语气
Right. But I think I perceived certain condemning tone
这不是犯罪，不过现在付你妻子的生活费会成问题
It is not a crime, but it's a problem at the time
to be pay the living of your wife
律师在谈Camila的生活费的事，包括衣服，学费...
The lawyer is talking about the living expenses of Camila
that includes clothes, school...
不好意思
Excuse me
从我认识我妻子开始我就已经每年都给她生活费了
I've been in charge of the yearly expenses of my wife
since I know her
我女儿也什么都不缺
And my daughter will not be missing anything
如果我有问题，别担心，我会处理好的
If I have a problem, don't worry because I'll fix it
幸运的是Malamut女士还真有份工作
Luckily Ms. Malamut DOES have a job at the moment
所以我们认为Fischer先生没有必要共享这份生活费
So we don't see the necesitty of granting Mr. Fischer
the shared expenses
对不起，不好意思
I'm sorry. Excuse me
我已经负担各种各样的费用很多年了
I've been in charge of everything for years
就这一个月她有工作我没有
And for a month where she has a job and I don't
我都没有权利分享我自己女儿的生活费
I don't have the right to share the expenses of my daughter?
我希望法官能考虑考虑这多不公平
I hope the judge will take into account
how unfair this situation is
法官不会考虑的是你对妻子使用的暴力
What the judge won't take into account is the violence
that you are using with your wife
什么暴力？
WHAT violence?!
我只是在描述一种情况，你在哪儿看见了暴力
I'm describing a situation.
Where do you see the violence?
我看暴力了，在很多地方
I see violence, Mr. Fischer.
In a lot of places
我看见街上有暴力，我看见电视上也有暴力
I see violence in the street.
I see violence when the TV is on
就说近处，我在报纸上就看见了
Without going very far. I can see it
in an article of this newspaper
我觉得这种情节小孩子还是少见为好
And I'm convinced that the less contact a small kid
can have with this type of episodes
为了他们的精神健康
It would be better for its psychophysical integrity
Victoria
你想把我女儿带走吗
Do you want to take away my daughter?
不，不是那样的
No, it's not that
那是什么样的？你傻了吗？
Then what is it?! Are you going nuts?
好吧，我和我的客户要终止这次调解
All right. My client and I will end the mediation
我们法院上再见吧
And we will mantain silence until we see each other in Tribunales
你就不说点什么吗？谁雇的你？她？
You're not planning to say anything?
Who hired you. Her?
Fischer先生，请冷静一下
Mr. Fischer, calm down. Please
-你好
-Hello
-晚上好
-Good evening
我是Simon Fischer,我和Ederer先生的秘书谈过
I'm Simón Fischer
I spoke with Mr. Ederer's secretary
-我就把简历留在这儿了
-I'm supposed to leave my resume
-当然可以，我会交给她
-Sure, I'll give it to her
我更希望自己交给她
I'd rather give it to her personally..
如果Ederer先生在这儿，我想跟他聊聊
and if Mr. Ederer's here,
I'd like to have a word with him
我在马丁内斯联营公司
I worked for over ten years...
工作了十多年
at Seijas Raffo Martinez and Associates
我不是新手
I'm not a rookie
工程师现在不在这儿
The engineer is on a construction site
-那他的秘书呢
-And his secretary?
-她出去吃午饭了
-She's out for lunch
现在是下午4点
It's 4 pm
我又不掌控她的行程
I don't handle her schedule
你猜怎样？我他妈的不会给你留下任何东西
You know what?
I won't leave you a damn thing
你，Ederer和他的秘书，都去你妈的
You can all go fuck yourselves:
you, Ederer and his secretary
尤其是他的秘书，所有人都去你妈的
Especially his secretary.
Everybody can go fuck themselves!
下午4点吃午餐？他们还真当我是傻子了
Lunch at 4 pm?
They must think I'm an idiot!
你的车是蓝色的雪佛兰吗
The blue Chevrolet?
你太没礼貌了，纯属是个法西斯主义者
You are being rude, and this is completely fascist
-我得先付钱再讨论？
-I have to pay first and discuss later
-当然
-Exactly
真是不撞南墙不死心
Until a tragedy happens you will not stop
这是恐怖分子袭击
[IT WAS A TERRORIST ATTACK]
国防部声明这是意外
[THE DEFENSE PROCLAIMS THAT
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT]
汽车移动导致爆炸事故，罪魁祸首曾是爆破工程师
[THE ENGINEER WAS WORKING WITH EXPLOSIVES.
THE MOVEMENT OF THE CAR CAUSED THE EXPLOSION]
律师回应：“该工程师事先计算过爆破半径，没有人员死亡即是证明。”
[THE ATTORNEY ANSWERS
"THE FACT THAT HERE ARE NO DEATHS PROVES
THAT THE ENGINEER CALCULATED THE RADIUS OF EXPLOTION]
这是他们第四次拖走我的车了！
#帮帮我炸弹仔
[IT'S THE FOURTH TIME THEY TAKE MY CAR!!!
#HelpMeBombita (Little Bomb)]
#炸弹仔 帮帮忙，炸掉经济部
[PLEASE #BOMBITA: BLOW UP THE
MINISTRY OF ECONOMY]
保险公司不愿赔偿
[INSURANCE COMPANY DOESN'T WANT TO PAY]
未能阻止此类事故发生，拖车公司应负责
[THE FAULT IS FROM THE TOWING COMPANY
FOR NOT STOPPING THIS TYPE OF ACCIDENTS]
人们怀疑拖车公司合同的合法性
[THEY ARE QUESTIONING THE LEGITIMACY
OF THE TOWING COMPANY'S CONTRACT]
社交媒体上一人称“炸弹仔”的工程师爆红，成千上万人要求保护其言论自由
[IN SOCIAL MEDIA, THOUSANDS OF USERS ASK FOR
THE LIBERATION OF THE ENGINEER POPULARLY CALLED "BOMBITA"]
#炸弹仔言论自由
[#BOMBITAFREE]
祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday to you!
生日快乐，炸弹仔
Happy Birthday Bombita!
Happy Birthday to you
爸爸
Dad
怎么了
What happened?
怎么了，Santiago
What happened, Santiago
说话呀
Speak!
向我保证他不会进监狱
Promise me they will not send him to jail
我们会尽全力的
We are going to make everything that's possible
刚不久解放者大街上发生过这类事件
It happened moments ago in the Libertador Avenue
司机碾过孕妇仓皇而逃，都没停下来救她
A driver ran over a pregnant lady and ran away
He didn't stop to help the victim
Santiago，到底发生了什么
Santiago, tell me the truth
你喝酒了吗？你抽大麻了吗
What did you drink.
Did you smoke weed?
车主身份尚不明确
The car was not able to be identified
警察正在分析监控录像
At this moment the police is analyzing
the security cameras
肇事逃逸。又一起布利诺斯艾利斯北部发生的悲剧
A hit and run. Another sad moment done by an
assassin in the north area of Buenos Aires
这车是谁名下的
Under what name is the car
-我的
-Mine
-留地址了吗
-And the adress under the car?
是这个
This one
我做了什么，我做了什么
What di I do, what did I do
你做了什么？你毁了我们的生活，混账
What did you do?
You ruined our lives, asshole!
-帮帮他，Mauricio
-Help him, Mauricio!
-带她走
-Take her away
Santiago,听我说，我需要你回答几个问题
Santiago, listen to me.
I need you to answer some questions
当时有人和你一起在车上吗
Did you have any passengers?
-你告诉过别人这件事吗
-Did you tell anybody about it?
-没有
-No
我们去看看这辆车
Let's go see the car
它装着有色玻璃
It has tinted windows
你记得窗户是升上来的吗
Do you remember if you had your windows up?
-我觉得是
-I think so
-再好好想想
-Please remember
是的，我把窗户升上去了
Yes, yes I had them up
你下车查看情况了吗，或者这是肇事逃逸吗
Did you went out to see what happened?
Or was it a hit and run?
肇事逃逸
Hit and run
你是从哪里过来的
And where were you coming from?
一个酒吧，在市区
From a bar, downtown
有人看见你开车来了吗，朋友或是什么女孩
Did anybody saw you come here with the car?
Friends, or any girls?
我不知道，不记得了
I don't know, I can't remember
刚有消息说孕妇和孩子已经在送往医院的路上死了
We were just informed that the woman and the baby
died on their way to the hospital
警察还在寻找证据
The police is still finding evidence
询问目击证人
And also asking different witnesses...
-谢谢，女士
-Thanks a lot, Mrs.
-不谢
-Please
给您这种建议真是太难为情了
I'm really embarassed
to propose this to you,
但是我们认识这么多年了
But we've known you for years
大家都像一家人了
And I feel we have this
kind of a bond
并且你是个父亲，你希望你的家庭能得到最好的
Besides you are a father,
and you want the best for your family
所以我觉得这样比较合适
So I think that an arrangement
like this one will help you
如果你说你昨晚趁家里人睡觉的时候开走了车
If you say that you took the car last night
while we were sleeping
事故发生的时候也是你在开车
And that you drove during the accident
我会找最好的律师让你尽快出监狱
I will place the best lawyer that will
get you out of jail as quickly as possible
态度良好的话不到一年半就能出来了
With good conduct you're out in less than
year and a half
-真这样吗
-Does it work that way?
-是的
-It does
帮我们这么大忙，我要给你五十万美元
And for that incredible favor
I'll offer you 500,000 dollars
你从来都没赚过那么多钱
You will never win that amount
of money with your job
下半辈子你就能让家里人接受良好的教育了
You will be able to provide good education
and well-being to your family for the rest of your life
你了解Santiago
You know Santiago.
他在监狱里过不下去的
He would not survive in a jail
Jose,请坐在车里
José, sit in the car please
两手握方向盘
Grab the steering wheel with both hands
尽可能多摸几下
Touch it as much as you can
很好
Good
你喝了一杯威士忌，你的老板睡着了
You drank a glass of whisky and your boss
was sleeping
当你像每个晚上那样停车的时候
When you came to park the car like every night
你想把车开出去试试
You felt the need to go drive outside
他们要是问起来，你就要说
If they were going to ask you about it,
what are you going to say
你去开车看看车胎性能怎么样
That you just went to check the tires
突然什么东西经过马路
Suddenly something crossed your path
你觉得颠了一下，不知道发生了什么
You felt a bump and from then on
you don't remember anything
是的
Yes
Jose,我不知道该怎么表达谢意
José, I can't explain how
grateful I am with you
别，别碰他
No, don't touch each other. Please.
没关系，女士
It's fine, Mrs.
对不起
Excuse me
我想...我不知道
I'm thinking that... I don't know
我想跟我妻子谈谈
I would like to talk it out with my wife
不要，她不能知道，至少现在不行
No. She can't know this, José.
At least for now
万一她说出真相怎么办，我们不能冒这种险
We can't run the risk if she talks
如果她说出真相，我们不会帮你，你还是会因为撒谎
And if she talks, the arrangement we did
finishes and you still go to jail
而进监狱
For lying
我亲爱的
My darling
你们两个开着我的SUV去农场
You two take my SUV and go to the ranch
经过收费站的时候别太显眼，也别在任何加油站停下
When you pass the tollbooth look down,
and don't stop at any gas station
想买什么只能付现金
And if you want to buy something
pay only in cash
Santiago，我们走
Santiago, let's go
我们走
Let's go
Jose，再坐到车里
José, sit again in the car
他坐在后排
He sits in the back
把座移到前面
Move the sit forward
你们两个快回房间睡觉
You two go to your room and go to bed
没人知道这件事
Nobody knows anything about this
冷静下来，保持沉默
Calm down and be quiet
我会处理好的
I'm in charge of this
Mauricio Pereyra Hamilton?
我是他的律师
I'm his lawyer
我正要叫警察，请进
I was about to call the police.
Please, come in
真是太惨了
What a horrible tragedy
大约一小时之前我的客户听见一楼有响动
About an hour ago my client heard something
in the first floor
他以为是小偷进来了
He thought that burglars were trying to get in
他下楼时看见了管家
When he goes down to see what happened
He finds the housekeeper
坐在我的客户的车里，喝醉了还受了惊吓
Sitting in his car, drunk and in shock
之后他看了新闻，推断出发生了什么，就马上给我打电话
Then he heard what happened in the news,
he connected everything and then he called me
Mauricio Pereyra.这是负责这起事件的律师
Mauricio Pereyra. This is the attorney
in charge of the case
-早上好
-Good morning
这就是Jose先生
And the gentlman here is José
-你好
-Hello
-他已经为这个家工作了...
-He has worked for the family for...
-15年吗
-...15 years?
-是的
-Yes
受害者的丈夫。先生，你对这件事怎么看
...The husband of the victim.
Sir, what's your reaction about this?
怎么看？我应该怎么看
What's my reaction about this?
How am I supposed to react
关掉电视，这没必要
Turn it off, it's unnecesary
我只想说一件事
...I'm only going to say one thing
不管是谁都要付出代价的
Whoever was it is going to pay for this
听见了吗？不管你藏在哪儿
Can you hear me? It doesn't matter
where you hide
我都会找...
I'm going to fi...
怎么了Jose
What happened, José?
不好意思，Jose，我想提醒你，你可以保持沉默
Excuse me. José. I want to remind you
that you can stay in silence
在我客户的要求下我要代表Torres先生
I'm going to represent Mr. Torres
by request of my client
没有问题，他还是两个儿子的父亲
There has never been a problem
and he is the father of two sons
你能告诉我这起事故的过程吗
Could you tell me the story of the accident?
可以，这个...
Yes, well...
我经常给Mauricio先生停车
I always park the car of Mr. Mauricio
我想开他的车兜风已经很久了
And for a while I always wanted
to take the new car for a ride
像宝马这种好车，开出去转转，你懂的
Run it a little, you know? The BMW
昨天晚上
And last night
说实话，我喝了点酒
I drank a little, to be honest
我感觉很兴奋就把车开出去了
And...well. I felt excited so I went out
我从来都没想过会发生什么不好的事
I never imagined that something wrong could happen
车开到解放者大街上，然后...
And I was going down Libertador Avenue, and..
我开得有点快了，说实话，非常快
And I was going a little fast, to be honest...
...Very fast
突然什么东西经过马路，我没看见
And suddenly something crossed my path.
I couldn't see what was it
我觉得那是条狗
I though it was a dog
我感觉车很重地颠了一下
I felt a very hard bump
我觉得我弄坏了Mauricio先生的车，我很怕
And I got scared because I thought
I ruined Mr. Mauricio's car
所以我想快点回去，在Mauricio先生醒来之前修好车
And I wanted to come back fast
so I could fix it before Mr. Mauricio woke up
不好意思
Excuse me
Jose,你能坐到前座上吗
José, would you be kind enough to sit
in the front seat?
-用握方向盘吗
-Do I touch it?
-是的，抓住方向盘
-Yes, grab the steering wheel
请靠在靠背上
Sit back, please
-能关下车门吗
-Could yo close the door?
-当然
-Sure
Jose,你用过后视镜吗
José. Do you ever use the rearview mirrors?
后视镜？当然啦，怎么可能不用
Rearview mirrors? Of course!
How am I not going to?
因为你在车里位置你只能看到车顶
Because in that position you can
only look at the ceiling
你只压到一个人真是个奇迹
It's a miracle that you only ran over
one person
可能他们跟着颠的那一下一起动了
May be they moved with the bump
他们都一起？
All of them at once?
好吧，你可能是对的
Yeah, you may be right
我觉得是一个比你高的人开的车
I would say that his car was drived
by someone taller than you
谁还住在这儿
Who else lives in this house?
我妻子和儿子，还有一条狗
Yes. My wife and son... The dog
让狗接着睡吧
Let the dog sleep
我想见见你的妻子和儿子
I'd like to meet your wife and son
当然可以，我会告诉他们你想见他们
Of course! I'll let them know that you
want to see them
我可以跟你商量一下吗
Do you give me permission
to make a negotiation?
怎么样了
How did it go?
很好
Everything's fine
他说事情有回旋的余地，但是...
He is willing to negotiate but...
代价可不便宜
it won't be cheap
多少钱
How much
-一百万
-One million
-美元？
-Dollars?!
他看你吃的住的知道你是个有钱人
He saw how you lived and
the house you've got...
他不会少要的
He won't ask for less
好事是他会打点一切
The good thing is that he will
be in charge of everything
他认识警长和大多数陪审团
He knows the chief of police,
most of the jury
他也帮我们圆这个谎
And he would help us reinforce
our story
那管家呢，他能被撇到这件事之外吗
The one of the housekeeper?
We cannot take him out of the deal?
不能，必须得有个肇事者为这件事负责
No, there has to be a responsible for this
这可是一尸两命，每个新闻台都在报道这件事
There were two deaths involved and it's
in every news channel
好吧，但是我没有那么多现金给他
That's fine, but I don't know if
I have that amount of money in cash
那可是一百万美元
It's 1.5 million dollars!
我知道，我那部分也在里面
I know, and my part is also in that
你那部分？
Your part?
我可是给你打点好所有事情的人
My part because I'm the person who is fixing
everything for you
我每年给你的公司那么多钱
I pay a lot of money to your firm every year
但这是另一回事,Mauricio
But that is for other things, Mauricio
这不是日常费用
This is not an every-day fee
我是冒着名声受损的危险
I'm risking my repuation here
我可是打算把我的车给你帮你家人逃跑的
I was about to give my SUV to your family
so they could escape
我觉得你可是不讲理了
I think your being inconsiderate
多少钱？
How much are talking
我不知道
I don't know...
再加五十万美元？
Another 500,000 dollars?
如果你想找别的律师，那也没关系
If you want to call another lawyer
it's fine,
我的工作已经做完了
My work would be done here
收拾好这摊子事
Go finish this
一切还好吗,Jose
Is everything fine, José?
其实不好
Actually, no.
为什么
Why?
坐两年牢，结果我和律师拿了一样多的钱？
For two years in jail I'm going
to get the same as that lawyer?
我知道我穷，但是...
I know I'm poor, but...
你知道你这样做很不好吗
Did you know it's very bad what you
ar doing now?
不好？
Bad?
这样的话你进监狱好了
In that cas you go to jail
昨晚我看了一部西部电影
Last night I watched a cowboy's movie
喝了点酒，像往常一样11点就睡了
I drank some liquor, and I was in bed by 11
like every night
你还想要什么快说
What else do you want?
要明白现在可没时间了
And be clear because there's no time
之前商量好的钱和...
The money we agreed and...
沙滩上的公寓
An appartment in the beach
Mauricio. José
我们能一起谈谈吗
Can we all have a talk?
Mauricio
正义，正义，正义
Justice! Justice! Justice!
咱们简短地谈一下，先生们
Let's talk fast, gentlemen.
因为我们没时间也不想有任何误会
Because we don't have a lot of time
And we don't want any misunderstandings
你之前编的那个故事不用改了
The story that you made up will not be changed
我会让你们一家人一会儿作证
I will ask you and your family to testify
in a few moments...
谁也不许走
So nobody goes anywhere
你会被拷起来蒙着头带走
You'll leave here handcuffed
and with your head covered
外面会有一大群记者和抗议民众
Outside we will find the news, a mob
他们会采访你，侮辱你
They're going to ask you things.
They're going to insult you
-但是你什么都不能说
-But you will not answer back
-好的
-Sure
我们得止住流言让事情顺利进行
We have to stop the rumors and let
the case go with no friction
让陪审团来判决，大家都会满意
Let the jury make the sentence and
everyone's happy
妈妈，停下
Mom, stop!
他说他想走出去认罪
He says he wants to confess
and go out in the street
这才是正确的
It's the right thing to do!
拜托，给他解释解释，他不懂
Please, explain him he doesn't understand
冷静，Santiago
Calm down, Santiago
你妈妈是对的
Your mom is right
一切都会好起来的
Everything will be fine
拜托你关上门，看好Santiago
Could you, please, close the door
and take care of Santiago?
-好的，我们走吧
-Yes. Let's go.
-别担心，Santi
-Don't worry, Santi.
我们能继续吗
May we continue?
你就是我们之间的联系了
From now on you'll be the connection
between all of us
我不会再见Pereyra先生，除非他出来作证
Me and Mr. Pereyra are not going to talk again
except when he declares the facts
你，Jose,除了你的律师以外不要和任何人说话
And you, José, stay away from all sort
of communication with anyone who isn't your lawyer
很好
Perfect
我需要一些钱来打通关系
I'm going to need some cash for
any expenses I have to pay
大概三万美元
Around 30,000 dollars
周一一大早就给我
That you'll send me on monday at
first hour of the morning
不好意思问一下...
I'm sorry I ask...
要打通什么关系
What would those expenses be?
外面都是警察
Outside there's the whole police
知道一些风声的人我们都要拉拢进来
If somebody saw or heard anything
we will have to put them in the story
这件事一定要把紧口风
We have to be ready against any loose
ends this story might have
-所以如果大家都同意的话...
-So if everyone agrees...
-周一一定把钱给你
-I'm sure that the money will arrive you on monday...
但是这得从给你的那一百万里出
But it comes out of the money
we talked earlier
我不会再多给一个子儿
I'm not paying one more cent
Mauricio，别这样
Mauricio, please stop
真的，别这样，我也想这样说，别这样
Exactly. Please stop! That's the same
thing I want to say. Please stop
要明白现在事情这么复杂
Understand that I'm in a complicated situation
但是我不会让你这样拿走我的钱
But I'm not going to let you
take my money like these
Mauricio，律师说得有理
Mauricio. What the attorney is saying
is understandable
别为三万美元斤斤计较
Don't let yourself go by 30,000 dollars
那你自己给他啊
Then pay them yourself
从我给你的钱里出
Pay them from your part
先生们，现在不是讨论这个的时候
Gentlemen, this is not the time for
a discussion like this
你想要做个了结，现在正是时候
If you want to finish, this is the time
或者为什么不从给你的钱里出，你也能拿一百万美元
Or why doesn't it come from your part.
You'll collect from this a million dollars
你还多要了三万美元
And you are asking me 30,000 more
for expenses
谁还拿了一百万美元？
Who is getting a million dollars?
不，他是对的
No. He's right.
就从那一百万里出
The million dollars includes expenses
打点费加给你的钱一共一百万
The expenses plus your part adds up
to a million
别动我那份钱，好吗
Don't touch my part, all right?
你们猜怎么样，伙计们
You know what, guys?
我受够了，没有商量的余地了
I'm done with this. There's no deal
别这样，Mauricio，什么叫没有商量的余地了？
No. Mauricio, what do you mean there's no deal
就这样，就这样，我不会给钱了
It's done. It's done. It's no more.
我谁的钱也不给了
They'll be nothing for anyone.
所有人的钱
Anyone!
Santiago!
你愿意认罪吗
Didn't you want to confess what you did?
很好，出去认罪吧
Sounds perfect. Go outside and do it.
我给了你最好的教育
I gave you the best education.
但你总是我行我素，现在快滚吧
And you always did whatever you wanted.
So now go fuck yourself!
Mauricio.
Mauricio，冷静地，我们再商量商量
Mauricio, calm down. Could we talked about it!
发生什么了
What happend? What happened?
他们就是群见钱眼开没人性的家伙
They are all a bunch of vultures.
就这样了
That happened.
不过都结束了，我可没撞死任何人
But it's over. I did not kill anyone.
Mauricio别这样，求你了
Mauricio I'm asking you, please!
今早我们在San Isidro的市中心，就是这起悲剧发生的地方
We are in the heart of San Isidro
where a tragic accident happened this morning...
Mauricio.
打开门，我有很重要的事要告诉你
Can you open the door? I have something important to tell you.
Mauricio.
我们能像文明人一样谈谈吗
Can we talk in a civilized way?
怎么了
What's up?
我们说好了，三万美元就能付清一切
It's done. We reached into an agreement
and the 30,000 dollars will be paid by all.
我什么也不想听了，都结束了，滚出我的房子
I don't want to hear anything else. It's over! Get out of my house.
我提醒你这可是一尸两命
Mauricio I remind you that there were two deaths.
如果Santiago被定罪了，我们会付更多的钱
If Santiago is found guilty this will cost us
a lot more.
然而，Jose很穷
However, José, is poor.
谁会赔偿死者家属呢
So who is going to pay the victims' families?
钱要给他们
The money should go there.
那个废物的工资是我给的
This piece of garbage has a salary that
comes out of my taxes.
好好想想是怎么回事
Go find out what happened.
你想给我儿子辩护，让他付律师费。要是他付得起，那也行
You want to defend my son, set your fees with him.
If he can afford it, I'm fine with it.
做你该做的事，辩护去
Do what you have to do. Go talk!
停在，我们已经商量好了，一个绅士可不会这样反悔的
Look. We already had a deal.
A gentleman wouldn't get out of it like this.
如果冒犯了真是对不起
I ask  for apologies if I offended you.
但是从我到这儿，我做的可只有为你的家庭辩护
But since I am here, I haven't done nothing else
but to defend your family.
真是谢谢你了，你可真是上帝派来的天使
I thank you a lot! You are an angel from God!
我能和他们谈谈吗
Will you let me talk to them?
也许有更好的解决办法
To see if I can improve the situation.
不好意思
Excuse me.
怎么了
Well.
我们有个更好的建议
I think we have a better proposal.
Jose愿意只要最初商定的五十万并且不要公寓了
José will accept the initial 500,000
and says you should forget the appartment.
我和律师一共一百万，不会再多一分钱
The attorney and I will share a million. The end.
Not one more cent.
我们得快行动了，媒体都在外面
We have to do it now, Mauricio. The news is outside.
律师说警察那儿不能再拖了
And the attorney says that he cannot delay
anymore the entrance of the police officer.
不行
No.
我一共给一百万
I'll pay a million in total.
你们自己随便分
And you share it however you want.
-怎么只有一百万了
-How come just a million?
-就这么多，爱要不要
-It's that or nothing.
行不行随你
If you like it, fine. If not, go away.
你们要是再有什么新花招，我就告你勒索
If you hit the door with any other deal
and I'll denounce you for extortion.
你和那个律师一起告
TYou and the attorney.
先生，你能透露肇事者的身份吗
Mr. Could yo reveal us the identity of the assassin?
现在无可奉告，我只能说案子基本有了结果
At the moment nothing will be said.
The only thing I can say is that the case is practically solved.
只有一个嫌疑人，他会受到法庭的判决
There is one single suspect and in a few moments
he will be presented to the judge
谢谢
Thank you very much.
Baldie，你每张照片里都光着身子
Baldie, you are naked in every picture!
现在
And now,
时候终于到了
The time has come
请全体起立
To stand up
欢迎
in order to receive
我们亲爱的
our dear
Romina和Ariel
Romina and Ariel.
我把岳父交给你了
I'll leave you my father-in-law.
我会盯着你的
I'll watch you
我可看着你呢
I'm looking at you
是的，是的
Yes, yes
谢谢
Thank you!
祝你今晚愉快
I wish you a happy evening!
大家看镜头
Everybody look at the camera.
威士忌
Whisky.
Whisky!
大家笑一笑
Let's see a smile.
太好了，谢谢
Very good. Thank you very much.
谢谢，非常感谢
Thank You. Thank you very much.
玩儿得开心
Well, enjoy.
Romina.
嗯？
Yes?
有个小礼物要给你
Here's a little present for you.
别这样，不用的
Oh, please. You didn't have to.
你能来就是很好的礼物了
The gift here is that you came.
-你们玩的开心吗
-Are you having fun?
-很开心
-Everything's beautiful.
你们一家人又善良又有趣
Your family is very kind and funny.
就是乡下治安不好
It's a shame the insecurity in the country
昨晚几个小偷趁他不注意偷走了钱包
Last night some burglars robbed his wallet
without him noticing.
天啊，真不敢相信
Oh, I can't believe it.
太糟糕了，不过，事情会慢慢...
Sounds terrible. Oh well, little by little...
-那些人，他们是你们的朋友吗
-Beautiful people. Are they friends?
-是的
-Yes.
好吧，那桌是乡下俱乐部的
Okay. That's the table of the guys from the country club.
我们13年没见了，不过通过脸书找到了他们
We had not seen each other for 13 years
but met up thanks to Facebook.
脸书
With Facebook.
后面的那些人是大学同学和她们的男朋友
The ones in the back are college friends with their boyfriends.
当然，有男朋友的才能带男朋友来，对吧
Well, the ones who have. Right?
那些是...
Those are ...
Ariel的同事
Coworkers of Ariel.
玩的开心吗
Are you having fun?
当然，你呢
Yes, you?
也是
Yes.
一切都...有板有眼的
Everything's very ... standard.
你真幽默
Your so much fun
-玩的开心
-Have fun.
-你也是
-You too.
你知道有什么学探戈的好地方吗
Do you know a good place to learn tango?
是...不知道
Yeah ... No.
不过我表妹肯定知道
No, but I assure you that my cousin does.
我把她找来
I'll present her to you.
你好
Hello.
哦，妈的
Oh, fuck.
怎么了
What happened?
我把酒拿走？
But... I'll take away the wine?
不，不是因为酒
No, it's not the wine.
别说话，别说话
Shut up, shut up
Ariel，是那个长头发的女孩？
Ariel, what's the name of the girl with long hair?
-哪个
-Which One?
-那个
-That one.
你的同事
Your coworker.
Lourdes.
怎么了
Why?
没事
No. No.
还有Lourdes怎么认识你的吉他老师
And how does Lourdes knows your guitar teacher?
什么，我的吉他老师
What, my guitar teacher?
我几个月前问你这是谁的号码，你说是吉他老师的
When I asked you a couple of months ago about this number,
you said it was your guitar teacher.
我觉得奇怪就存了那个号码
Since I found it strange I saved the number.
我给你吉他老师打电话竟然是那个叫Lourdes的女孩接的，真是奇怪，不是吗
And it's weird that when I call him this girl, Lourdes, answers.
Right?
-我不知道你在说什么
-I have no idea what you're talking about.
-你不知道我在说什么？
-You don't know what I'm talking about?
我是说，Ariel
About that, Ariel
有那么多手机公司
That with all the celular companies that exist
生产的那么多手机，怎么那个女孩的手机号会跟你吉他老师的号是一样的
And all the promotions they have, it's weird that this girl
has the same telephone number as your guitar teacher.
特别是他们从没见过
Especially if they have never met
这真是个巧合
Isn't it an incredible coincidence?.
-所以呢
-So?
-什么
-What?
给我个答案，否则我就去问她
Give me an answer, or otherwise I'll go ask her.
-Romi,别...
-Romi, please ...
-Romi也他妈的是你叫的？
-"Romi" Fuck off!
回答我
Answer my question.
Ariel
27号桌所有人是不是都知道你和那个女孩鬼混过
Does the entire table 27 knows that you've fucked that girl?
你把这些混蛋都请到婚礼上了？你干了什么？
Did you invite all those assholes to our marriage? What did you do?
对不起打扰一下
Sorry to interrupt.
能和我们的王子跳个舞吗
Would allow me a dance with the prince?
当然，我的皇后
Of course. My queen!
你的王子在这儿
Here is your prince.
怎么了
What happened?
Romi，你还好吗
Romi, are you okay?
怎么了
What happened?
稍等
One second, please.
Romi.
Baldie，能让我和她再跳一支舞吗
Baldie, would you let me one more dance?
我亲爱的
My love.
亲爱的，停下
Honey, stop it.
高兴点
Let's enjoy the party.
你和那个婊子在一起吗
Were you with that bitch?
求你了，别这样
Please, I beg you!
我得知道
I need to know!
是的，我是和她在一起
Yes, I was.
但对我来说这什么也不算
But for me it meant absolutely nothing.
Romi，这么多人这样不好
Romi, please don't make a scene in front of everyone.
我太蠢了，对不起，我错了
I was stupid. I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
我想一个人静静
I want to be alone.
-怎么了
-What's up?
-你看见她了吗
-Did you see her?
你问我？
You are asking me?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我需要叫谁过来吗
Should I call someone?
但是你还好吗
But are you okay?
你肯定不好
Obviously you're not.
不
No.
冷静，怎么了
Calm down, what happened?
我刚知道我丈夫在和一个婚礼上的客人偷情
I just learned that my husband is cheating on me with another guest.
哦，那太糟了
Oh, that's bad.
我知道该怎么办
And now I don't know what to do.
那么多人都看着
With all the people there.
放松，这种事情经常发生
Relax, these things happen.
时间过去就好了
They're overcomed with time.
给你
Here.
如果你爱他，从长远角度来想你要原谅他
If you want him, on the long run you'll be able to forgive him.
-你爱他吗
-If hee is your husband.
我不知道我爱不爱他
-No, I do not know if he is what I want.
我不知道他是不是对的人
I don't know if he's my man.
他就是个混蛋
He is an asshole.
哦，好吧
Oh, well.
这样的话抓好机会
In that case take the opportunity.
别担心那些客人，你不是第一个被伴侣背叛的人
And th guests? Well, don't feel like you were the first ont to be cheated on.
还有，你要是太在意别人怎么想...
Also, if you are going to care so much of what others say then ...
你就完了，亲爱的
You're done, darling
好点了吗
Are we cool?
听着
Look.
如果我是你我就回去
If I was you I go there.
让婚礼快点结束
I accelerate everything so the party finishes early,
然后，第二天晚上
and then, the next night at home,
你就和他分手。你经历的事情很糟糕
you break up with him. What happened to you is terrible.
我不否认
I will not deny it.
但是生活需要继续
But you must move forward.
好点了吗
Better?
Romina?
你现在就离开这儿，什么也不要说
You leave right now from here and you don't say a word!
你不明白你惹了谁
You don't have any idea of who you are dealing with!
我要拿走你所有的钱
I'll get every cent from you,
为了逃避财务部，我会拿走你父亲给你买的每一处房产
I'll get every single property that your father has bought for you
in order to evade the Treasury.
我们可结婚了呀
We are married,
合法婚姻
Legally married.
我会和那些即使只在乎我一点点的人睡觉
I will dedicate my days to sleep with every person who gives a minimum shit about me.
不管是谁，只要有一点点爱我就行
With whoever who gives me athe most little gram of love.
当你想离婚的时候
And when you want to have a divorce,
我要去上几节表演课
I'll take acting classes
在法官面前装可怜
to sit in front of the judge with a puppy face,
告诉他我在抵抗，在挣扎
and tell him that I'm fighting, I'm struggling.
这样我们的婚姻就会无限期地延长
That way our marriage is prolonged indefinitely.
我要在脸书上泄露你所有的秘密
I will divulge all your secrets through Facebook,
我要折磨到你痛不欲生
I'll put my finger in the cut and stir it until cry you of pain.
你要受到巨大的羞辱
You'll go through so many humiliations,
你逃脱的唯一方法就是跳下这阳台
that your only escape will be throw yourself off the balcony.
到那时候，死亡将我们分开
And then, when death do us part,
你的死将我们分开
when YOUR death do us part,
我就得到了一切
I'm getting with everything.
Ariel!
Ariel,冷静
Ariel, calm down.
快走，瘦猴儿
Come on, skinny.
快走，快走
Go, go.
Ariel.
小婊砸，你上哪儿了？你还好吗？
Bitch! Where were you? Everything's okay?
放我下来，你们这群混蛋
Bring me down, assholes!
你们疯了，听不见吗
Idiots! Are you listening?!
放我下来
Get me off!
他在说什么？
What is he saying?
-Ariel，当心
-Ariel, watch out.
-操你妈的
-Fuck you!
混蛋
Asshole!
放我下来
Bring me down!
你要走了吗
Are you already leaving?
别啊，来玩啊
Please, no. Come.
-不了，这...
-No, it's ...
-真的，没事儿
-Seriously, everything's fine
来啊，Lour
Come with me, Lour.
快停下，我好晕
Please stop. I'm getting dizzy.
这太棒了
This is great!
真的，快停下
Stop it! Seriously!
你去过我们的俱乐部吗？或者你还太小？
Did you used to go to our club, or were you younger.
你知道俱乐部是因为有人被打了才关的吗
Did you know that they closed it because
someone got kicked there?.
她威胁他说她要拿走他的每一处房产
She threatened him saying she was going to get everything
up to his last property.
是的，这样更好
...Yes, it's better.
我为发生的事情感到抱歉
I'm deeply sorry for what happened.
不过，婚礼很棒
However, the party was wonderful.
不好意思
Excuse me, please.
大多数都是皮外伤
Most of wounds are superficial.
会好的
They will heal well.
不过我们还是要检查一下有没有肌腱被割断
However, we will still take to ensure that she did not cut any tendons.
她上保险了吗
Does she have a good insurance company?
Romina，别这样
Romina, Please ...
回大厅去
Go back to the hall!
我就是想知道她上保险了吗
I'm just wondering if she has a good insurance company.
好主意，待在里面
Sounds good. Stay inside!
我没事儿
I'm fine.
Romi,亲爱的，你还好吗
Romi, dear. Are you okay?
好，好，冷静
Yeah yeah. Stay calm.
我们来玩蛋糕吧
What if we use this hole for the cake?
来啊，姑娘们，别让我一个人傻站在这儿
Come on, girls. Do not leave me standing like this.
来啊，姑娘们
Come on, girls.
我刚才感觉很糟，但是我知道怎么在婚礼上玩得高兴
I had a very shitty moment but now I want to enjoy
my marraige.
我觉得我不会再结婚了
I do not think I'll get married again.
准备好了吗
Ready?
Romi.
我的天啊，Mili，你？
Oh my God, Mili. You?
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我要和Mili拍照
A picture with Mili.
拍照
Picture.
你想娶Mili?
Do you want to marry Mili?
哦，不是,Romi!
Oh, no, Romi!
让大家看看这一切都是假的
Let's show that everything here is a lie,
但是戒指是真的
but that the ring is true.
这不是很棒吗
Wouldn't it be great?
Romi,别这样
Romi, stop
吻她，吻她
Kiss her! Kiss her!
-Romina
-Romina.
-怎么了
-Yes?
花束送来了，狂欢也要开始了
Now comes the bouquet and the Rio carnival ...
不知道你还想不想继续了
I don't know if you want to continue or...
暂停吧
Suspend it.
结束吧
End it.
为什么，问什么你一副苦瓜脸
But why? Why are you being so bitter?
姑娘们，接着！
Girls, here it goes!
熏牛肉还没上呢，不是吗
We are also missing the pastrami, right?
你知道我们花了多少钱吗
You know how much did it cost?
说实话，Ariel
Say the truth, Ariel.
我们为熏牛肉争执了一个星期
We argued for a whole week about the hot pastrami.
我们已经买了就要吃了它，这不对吗，先生？
We decided to pay for it and now I want to eat it. Is it possible, sir?
Romina,别这样
Romina. Stop!
让大家回家吧
Let the people go home.
你不是在犯傻吗
Isn't it a stupid thing what you are doing now?
给你个建议，我家的律师说我们可以告你威胁我们
To give you an idea, my family lawyer says we should sue you for threats you made.
别告诉我这是你妈妈的主意
Don't tell me this was a plan from your mom.
Romina,我是认真的，别这样了
Romina, seriously. Cut it.
你妈妈真是个...
Your mom is a real ...
-婚礼策划者
-wedding planner.
-停下
-Stop it!
我对你做了什么
What did I do to you?!
对于你做的那些事来说，我做的事简直不足挂齿
I didn't do anything compared to what you're doing to me!
亲爱的
Dear.
拜托，冷静一下
Please, I ask you to stay calm.
拜托
Please.
我的天啊
Oh my God ...
拍下来，Nestor
Shoot this, Néstor.
Nestor,快拍下来
Nestor, shoot this please.
你也是，快点
You too, come.
拍下来
Shoot, please.
如果我再结婚
If I get married again,
如果我能找到一个值得我嫁的男人
If I get a guy who's worth it,
我要把这一幕放在大屏幕上
I'll put this as a blooper on the big screen.
不
No...
我还要和我的孩子一起看
I'll even watch this with my kids.
除了该死的《爱探险的朵拉》，我还要放这段视频
Instead of fucking Dora The Explorer, I'll put this video.
我知道
I know!
我要把这段电子影像连着播放
I'll put in those electronic portraits that go on a loop
整天都放
all day.
把你的手从我女儿身上拿开，贱货
Get your hands off my daughter, bitch!
你最好滚开
You better get the fuck away
我是来帮忙的，Baldie
I'm here to help, Baldie!
放开她
Leave her
亲爱的，你还好吗
Darling, are you okay?
医生
Doctor!
照顾好那位女士，你去看看那个先生
Take care of the lady, please. You deal with the gentleman.
他喝了什么
What did he drink?
没什么，被吓到了
Nothing. Emotional shock.
你能走路吗
Can you walk?
-来，到这儿
-Here, over here.
-你好，Romina
-Hello, Romina.
请冷静下来，我要测你的血压
I'm going to ask you to calm down. I'm going to take your pressure, okay?
Romina
请坐
Sit here.
请把他的外套脱下来
Can you take his blazer off, please.
坐下，Romina
Take a sit, Romina
坐下
Sit down
你还好吗，别着急，冷静
Are you okay? Don't worry, Calm down.
Romina.
能给我倒杯水吗
Can I bother you with a glass of water?
当然
Yes, please.
哦，不，Romi,不
Oh, no. Romi, no.
别担心，Romi
Don't worry, Romi
等等，Ariel
Wait, Ariel
冷静Ariel
Calm down, Ariel.
小声点，小声点
Quiet, quiet.
没事，我们很好
Nothing happened, we're fine.
-安静
-Quiet.
-没事
-It's okay.
由他去吧
Let him be
停下Ariel,停下
Stop, Ariel. Stop.
不，Ariel!
No! Ariel!
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org